[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Why do you want to do this interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I think the tide has turned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Has your family had death threats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Credible threats?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Credible threats.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Against others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "You know, I'm really not at liberty to discuss exactly who was threatened or how they were threatened, but I can tell you that I, myself, have been contacted by law enforcement, too, because there was credible intelligence that could threaten me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Why would your brother do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Well, you know, taking, from what you said, when you said chasing after and getting into an altercation, there's a lot of ways that people get into altercations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "You, personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Me, personally, I heard immediately after the incident.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Within an hour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "I would say within 24 hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "So the next day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Would be the closest I'm willing to narrow the window down of exactly when George spoke, yes, would be within the next 24 hours.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "And what exactly did he tell you about what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Well, some of the details have come out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Which way is he running?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Down towards the entrance of the neighborhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "NNP", ":", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 121, "question": "When you say he stopped following, how do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I believe that's what George -- and that's what's in the police reports and that's what has been leaked and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "It's only George's word, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["Mr. Crump"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "What did George tell you Trayvon Martin allegedly did to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "What has come out that I can talk about today is that Trayvon Martin somehow snuck up on him, and according to Mr. Crump, their own attorney, he was on -- we don't know if this is verifiable information, but he was on the phone with his girlfriend.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What did George tell you he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "One of those things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "And when you say \"attacked,\" what did George tell you Trayvon did to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "``", "VBN", ",", "''", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, I don't know, I believe that at the time, George knew he had sustained some kind of injury to his face or his nose.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "How do you explain that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "We're confident the medical records are going to explain all of George's medical history, because how he was treated at the scene and how he was not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Have you talked to George about the video since it came out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I'm not at liberty to say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Does he have any injuries now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "His nose is still broken.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "It's still broken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "His nose is still broken, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "A month later, it's still broken?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "His nose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Would you not, at the very least, if you're honest and candid about this, would you not have expected that person to at least be arrested, to at least perhaps face some kind of trial where the full evidence could come out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "VB", "VBN", ",", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, and -- you know, I take a -- I take a pause to that whole, you know, conjecture, again, of pulled out a gun and shot him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "That's not what happened, then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "No, it is not what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "But he did pull out a gun and shoot him, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, he stopped someone from disarming him and shooting him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "But he had the gun on him, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "He had a permit to carry that gun --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "NN", ":", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Where was the gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "The gun, I believe, was in his -- inside -- tucked inside his pant waist --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "So he has pulled it out and he has fired it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Well, he has taken control of his firearm, he prevented his firearm from being taken from him and used against him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "That Trayvon was trying to grab his gun to use against him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "My father also is on record yesterday night saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Do you need police, fire, or medical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "CD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Maybe both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "That's my brother.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "What else could it have been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "It could have been anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What do you think he's saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "That part -- that tape, it's my understanding, is not actually in the original 911 tapes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What do you think you heard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Right, I believe --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Or what do you think those two words were?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "IMMERMAN: Again, I just -- I don't believe that, first of all, that they're words.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "But what do you believe he was saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "I have no idea that he was even saying anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Have you ever heard your brother utter a racist remark about anybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I mean, you can't blame Trayvon Martin for wondering what the hell this guy's doing or who he is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, you know, sadly, even your statements now are just a product of conjecture.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you believe that it was actually, with hindsight, a mistake for the police to effectively conclude on the night, he had no case to answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Yes, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Has George ever lied to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Not to my knowledge, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "He's always been completely, 100 percent honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "He's -- he would be the more honest of the two.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "To his mother in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, to his mother, you know, personally, myself, I can't speak for George, this is a tragedy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What did you make of the interview that I just had with George Zimmerman's brother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What do you think happened, from everything you've seen and read?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I don't know what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Do you believe that any kind of altercation, if Trayvon was unarmed, justifies somebody shooting him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Well, I just know that young man shouldn't be dead from this ordeal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "It doesn't matter what I believe or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "How did he know that he had a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "To go for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Is this a law that should exist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you think America, Mike, has become more or less racist since Barack Obama, an African-American, became president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "There's a great possibility, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike", "Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "That it's become worse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "One hundred percent, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "How do you think Barack Obama's doing as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Now that your life has changed, and you have to pay bills, and you have to think about money and all those things, very different to when you had half a billion dollars and so on -- now that you're in that position and you can relate probably much better to people on the street, going through hardship, not having jobs and so on, do you think America is coming out of the bad times or do you think that it's still pretty set in the bad times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["a billion dollars"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "How has she changed you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "That's -- like that -- you can't even fathom the ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What effect did that tragedy have on you, did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "To be a parent and losing a child, it's so unnatural, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I don't know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "What kind of parent have you become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "I'm trying to become more understanding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Do you miss that kind of wealth, or is it destructive, that kind of money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "No, I just miss having this whole ordeal with my family that I never had before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "How has she made you come to peace with yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I don't know if I'm ever at peace with myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Do you still feel rages, occasionally, like you used to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Periodically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "When you look back at your life, what is the period you're most ashamed of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "When you look back on that, is that part of the problem, that you have people who just, they make money out of you being like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, of course I'm not that way anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "What reaction have you had from people to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "If I could replay a moment for you now, you could relive, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "YSON: I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Do you think Cus D'Amato, who was this legendary trainer -- do you think he would look at the way Mike Tyson is today and feel that you finally worked that out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "No, he'll find something else wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cus D'Amato", "Mike Tyson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "But he'd be proud of you, wouldn't he, for the way that you have rebuilt your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "He'd be very happy by the way I'm trying to rebuild my relationship with my children and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Was he the father figure that you never really had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "There's no doubt about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "When you have that kind of respect from somebody like him, it makes all the difference, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "No doubt about it, because that was my goal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120329pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "When you became world champion for the first time, what did that moment feel like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]